Your privacy is important to us and we are committed to protecting your information. We recognize that our customers' personally identifiable information deserves protection. This privacy policy applies to all information collected or submitted on **EUREKA.org** or **EUREKAExpress.org**.

If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that the information you provide to us is transmitted to and processed in the United States. Data will be protected subject to this Privacy Policy and applicable law, which may be different from the laws in your country. By using **EUREKA**, you agree to this.

Information Provided by Schools and Districts ("Sites")
-------------------------------------------------------

When Sites decide to subscribe to **EUREKA**, they submit information necessary to create their school account, including first and last names, email addresses, and phone numbers of the site coordinator and staff contacts, and the school, district or agency mailing address. Single license user subscriptions are also available.

Information Provided by Students and Clients ("Users")
------------------------------------------------------

Users create their own user name and password to log into **EUREKA** using a code or link provided by the Site. In addition to user name and password, users enter their email, age range, gender and demographic information. Age, Gender and Demographic information is private for the User and only used for statistical purposes.

**EUREKA** Usage Information and Cookies
----------------------------------------

When using **EUREKA**, our server automatically collects the Internet Protocol ("IP") address associated with the user's computer. We may also collect additional information such as login timestamp, the browser type and version, and the operating system of the computer. This information is logged to help us to diagnose technical problems and to administer the **EUREKA, CCIS websites**.

To collect information about the use of **EUREKA's websites**, we use cookies. Cookies are small data files sent by a website or application and stored on the computer or device at the request of that site or app. Cookies store information related to the browser to enable us to recognize the browser on return visits to our websites and to remember your preferences. We use third-party service providers to assist us in collecting and understanding the usage information. Most browsers can be set to detect browser cookies and to let you reject them but refusing cookies may make it difficult to use **EUREKA.org** or **EUREKAExpress.org**. To learn more about browser cookies, including how to manage or delete them, look in the Tools, Help or similar section of your Web browser.

How We Use and Disclose Information
-----------------------------------

**WE DO NOT SELL DATA**, and we do not use personally identifiable information for commercial purposes. In addition, we do not disclose, distribute, access or reference any personal information except as noted at the time that we request the information or in the following circumstances:

* To our third-party service partner, Reference Service Press ("RSP"), to permit them to provide features and services on our behalf and as requested by Sites (see Third Party Services section).
* When a Site has specifically requested the availability of RSP that allows their users to connect with it.
* When a Site staff person has specifically requested a list of specific site user login names and passwords.
* Site staff for **EUREKA.org** have access to the following Site User information:
    * User first and last names.
    * User emails.
    * User assessment results.
    * User saved information.
* Site staff for **EUREKAExpress.org** have access to the following Site User information:
    * User first and last names.
    * User emails.
    * User login names and passwords.
    * User assessment results.
    * User saved information.
        * To resolve a problem or support issue on behalf of a Client.
        * To investigate a suspected violation of the Terms of Service.
        * As may be required by law or as ordered by a court, in which event we shall notify Sites and shall work with Sites to seek to limit the scope of the required disclosure.
        * In the event of a reorganization, merger, sale, assignment, bankruptcy or other disposition of our business, in which case the transferred information will remain subject to the terms of this **Privacy Policy**.

We may use non-personal information, including aggregated, de-identified data for a variety of purposes subject to applicable law, including:

* to improve our educational products for adaptive learning purposes and for customizing the student experience
* to demonstrate the effectiveness of **EUREKA**, including in our marketing materials
* to develop and improve our products

How Clients Can Modify Information
----------------------------------

**EUREKA** Sites may update or change their institution's information by contacting us, or in some cases, updating their records through the relevant areas of **EUREKA**. We also provide Sites with a dashboard that allows them to access, modify and delete student and client information, as may be required by law or otherwise deemed necessary from time to time.

**EUREKA** Users have the ability to access or modify their information.

On some pages of **EUREKA.org** or **EUREKAExpress.org**, you can order products or materials or make direct requests. The types of personally identifiable information collected on these pages may include your name, e-mail and phone number. **EUREKA** uses this information to fulfill your requests for products, services and materials, and to contact you about updates and new products. All business transactions are done through PayPal. **EUREKA** never collects credit/debit card information. **EUREKA** maintains commercially reasonable safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of your personally identifiable information.

In order to do so, **EUREKA** may disclose certain of your personally identifiable information to necessary third parties **only**, such as **PayPal** and product suppliers.

Security
--------

We are committed to protecting the security, integrity and confidentiality of the data through the use of physical and technical safeguards. **EUREKA** uses a Dedicated Server hosted by Alentus, Transport Layer Security (TLS) encryption and server authentication technology to protect data when **EUREKA** is accessed using a supported web browser.

We host Sites data in secure server environments that use a firewall and other industry-standard technology in an effort to prevent interference or access from outside intruders. We also require unique account identifiers, user names, and passwords that must be entered each time Users sign on to **EUREKA**. The Internet, however, is not perfectly secure and **EUREKA** is not responsible for security breaches not reasonably within its control.

We require that Sites maintain the confidentiality of their user names and passwords. If Sites become aware of any unauthorized use of an account, loss of their or their users' account credentials or suspect a security breach, notify us immediately.

Data Retention Policy
---------------------

As a system of record for its Clients, **EUREKA** retains the data at the sole discretion of Sites, and for as long as they have active subscriptions for **EUREKA**. After termination of an agreement, **EUREKA** will retain Site data for a limited time period in accordance with the **EUREKA** Data Retention Policy for the convenience of Sites, so that they may retain continuity of their experience should they choose to reengage with **EUREKA**. At the end of the data retention period, we securely delete and destroy personal information from Sites.

Sites have total control over their data from users and the duration of their accounts. The data will always remain under the direct control of the Sites and subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

Notwithstanding the above, we do retain aggregated, de-identified data for the sites to use for statistical purposes.

EUREKA regularly deletes all personal information for cancelled accounts and sites, and will delete personal information upon request.

Under no circumstances does **EUREKA** sell private information to any concerns.

Opt-Out Policy
--------------

We send emails to individual contacts from Sites with information about our websites through Constant Contact. These individuals may opt out of receiving email messages at any time by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link found at the bottom of every email that we send.

If Clients have opted out of receiving communications from us, we may still send essential communications to our primary contacts for **EUREKA** regarding any of their Site's accounts, such as password change messages.

We do not send email messages on behalf of third parties.

Updates to This Policy
----------------------

**EUREKA** may amend its privacy policy from time to time without advance notice to you. If **EUREKA** decides to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, **EUREKA** will notify you by way of an email. You will have a choice as to whether or not **EUREKA** may use your information in this different manner. Otherwise, **EUREKA** will use all personally identifiable information only in accordance with the privacy policy in effect when such information was collected. Notwithstanding the foregoing sentence, **EUREKA** reserves the right to use your personally identifiable information in cooperation with any state, local, and federal officials in any investigation relating to any Content (including personal or private electronic communication transmitted on **EUREKA.org** or **EUREKAExpress.org**) or purported unlawful activities of any user.
